<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Engineers United Docs</title>
    <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Engineers United Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://engineers-united.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/posts/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/posts/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/engineers-united/get-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/engineers-united/get-involved/</guid>
      <description>Get Involved Getting started The History of HackUNT
It&amp;rsquo;s not required to know the history of HackUNT to get involved in it; nevertheless, it will give you perspective on where we started and where we are going.
 HackUNT History  How to get involved New Member I&amp;rsquo;m new&amp;hellip; now what?  Read the documentation on your role in the HackUNT/roles/ section Coordinate with the president about what is needed from you Attend the meetings Have fun, and enjoy the experience!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/engineers-united/git-workflows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/engineers-united/git-workflows/</guid>
      <description>Our Git Workflows Setting up git on your system Linux Linux For Fedora (or RPM-based distributions) RUN
sudo dnf install git-all For Debian-based distributions (such as Ubuntu) RUN:
sudo apt-get install git-all MacOS MacOS  If brew is already install in on your machine skip to Install git
 Install brew RUN
/bin/bash -c &amp;#34;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Homebrew/install/HEAD/install.sh)&amp;#34; Install git RUN
brew update brew install git brew install git-gui Windows Windows Install Git  Download the office installer by going here Choose either the 32-bit or 64-bit install After downloading, click yes to confirm changes Click Next &amp;gt; choose a folder for the location of Git Leave all checkboxes clicked by default &amp;gt; Click Next Click Next Choose a default text editor you want to use &amp;gt; Click Next Let Git Decide &amp;gt; Click Next Leave the default options and Click Next three times For Configuring the line ending conversions  Choose Checkout Windows-style, commit Unix-style line endings If there are any issues later down the road with committing, go to Working with multiple terminals   Click Next till the end and then click Install After installing, you can View release notes and/or Launch Git Bash   To verify Git install go to command prompt</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/example/shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/example/shortcodes/</guid>
      <description>Buttons Buttons are styled links that can lead to local page or external link.
Buttons Example {{&amp;lt; button relref=&amp;#34;/&amp;#34; [class=&amp;#34;...&amp;#34;] &amp;gt;}}Get Home{{&amp;lt; /button &amp;gt;}} {{&amp;lt; button href=&amp;#34;https://github.com/alex-shpak/hugo-book&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}Contribute{{&amp;lt; /button &amp;gt;}}  Get Home  Contribute   Columns Columns help organize shorter pieces of content horizontally for readability.
{{&amp;lt; columns &amp;gt;}} &amp;lt;!-- begin columns block --&amp;gt; # Left Content Lorem markdownum insigne... &amp;lt;---&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- magic separator, between columns --&amp;gt; # Mid Content Lorem markdownum insigne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/checklist/</guid>
      <description>HackUNT Checklist This checklist is everything I can remember that needs to be done to make HackUNT possible.
This list is not in order it is just everything I can remember and will be added to as needed.
 Hack UNT Operations  Typeform Set up for Registration Pick a theme for the event Make Sponsor Packet ( Use Canva ) Make Sponsor Onboarding Packet Pick a date for the event  Set up the event on Org Sync ( you will need to keep up with this and answer their comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/day-of-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/day-of-action/</guid>
      <description>Day Of Actions Check-in Station ( 2 - 3 People )   This person will be in charge of getting Check-in operational on the day of the event.
  Checking with Volunteers, Hackers, and Sponsors when arriving.
  Be sure to be kind and understanding if there is an issue feel free to let ( Andy / Nick ) know so we can mitigate any fallout.
  Check-in List Hacker</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/event-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/event-wifi/</guid>
      <description>Event WiFi Event WiFi is supplied by the UNT IT department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/roles/design-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/roles/design-team/</guid>
      <description>Design Team Phase 1  Create and finalize logo Create and finalize brand Make brand guidelines Make event flyers Make sticker design Make badge design Make volunteer promotion flyer Make Website mockup Make Livesite mockup  Phase 2  Get Speaker schedule from external relations Make speaker infographic Get judge panel and make bios from external relations Get Staff bios Get Tech Sponsors Get food sponsors from external relations Get Registration time Get prizes  Phase 3  Make event map with president Make T-Shirt design Make guide book template Collaborate and finalize the 5 guidebooks  (sponsors, attendees, volunteers, mentors, and hackers) with the president    Continuous  Make 20 social media posts Post other Hackathons on social media Post on Facebook, Instagram, and Snapchat each week  5 bio posts 2-3 registration posts 2-3 speaker posts 2-3 food posts 1 prize post 1 volunteer post 2-3 sponsor posts    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/roles/external-relations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/roles/external-relations/</guid>
      <description>External Relations  Find and Finalize 5 judges Reach out to 10 potential mentors a week Create a workshop schedule Find 10-20 workshop speakers Contact 10 tech sponsors a week Contact 2 food sponsors a week/get quotes Get T-Shirt quotes Get Sticker sponsor Get Badge quotes Contact News Sources  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/roles/president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/roles/president/</guid>
      <description>President Phase 1  Finalize Date Find and Finalize Venue Find and Finalize Tables, Chairs, and Cords Find and Finalize Internet Find and Finalize Power Create initial Budget Sheet  Phase 2  Talk to CSCE about collaborating  Sponsorship Mentors Volunteers   Talk to the College of Engineering  Sponsorship Mentors Volunteers   Talk to UIS about collaborating  Sponsorship   Talk to DAIR about collaborating  Sponsorship   Talk to the President about collaborating  Sponsorship    Phase 3  Collaborate with the brand director to make an event map Innovate and check on other processes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/email-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/email-templates/</guid>
      <description>Email Templates Following up We should follow up with sponsors after our event. It is important to know what we did right and did wrong. This will better help us to understand the wants and needs of our sponsors. These companies were willing to give us a chance and give us a considerable amount. It is important that we try to mitigate all damages that might have occurred during the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/initial-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/initial-outreach/</guid>
      <description>Initial Outreach </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Onboarding Packet Sponsorship Onboarding is the next step after sponsors agree to participate in the hackathon! It is very important that you follow up quickly and respectively during these times. Sponsors will have quite a few questions but most can be answered by giving them the Sponsor Onboarding Packet.
What is included in a good onboarding packet  Nice photo on the first page Welcome page with next steps Have information discussing how to build a custom challenge, picking a winner, and offering a prize Have three goals you want for the sponsor  i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Sponsorhip Retrospective Following up We should follow up with sponsors after our event. It is important to know what we did right and did wrong. This will better help us to understand the wants and needs of our sponsors. These companies were willing to give us a chance and give us a considerable amount. It is important that we try to mitigate all damages that might have occurred during the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/sponsorship-packet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/sponsorship-packet/</guid>
      <description>Sponsorship Packet Send this document during the initial reaching out to both legacy and potential sponsors. If this packet is done correctly, your sponsorship sells itself.
What is included in a good sponsorship packet  Main section stating we are a non-profit and go over our mission statement What is a hackathon Where are we located Make sure to included as much stats as reasonable Table of Sponsorship Benefits Why you should be a sponsor section Explain why there sponsorship is needed Send of message (optional) past sponsors section  Examples  2023 2022  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/stats/</guid>
      <description>Stats Stats must be updated yearly
It&amp;rsquo;s best to update the yearly stats as soon as possible, and or after the hackathon.
 Yearly Registration/Attendess Stats    Year Registration Attendess Ratio     2018 ? 248 N/A   2019 498 258 51.81%   2020 558 220 39.43%   2021 ? ? N/A   2022 ? ? N/A    Yearly Marketing Totals Stats    Year Ongoing Resumes Projects Attendess Prizes awarded     2018 1 ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/volunteer-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/volunteer-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Volunteer Guidelines Pre-Event or Pre-Shift  Familiarize self with Event Action Plan Have knowledge of severe weather safety areas at Discovery Park 1st floor Identify:  Fire Extinguisher locations Automated External Defibrillators ( used to treat sudden cardiac arrest) Manual Fire Alarm Pull Stations at exits First Aid Kits     During Event  Report to your section and let the previous volunteers/organizers know you are there for the shift.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>