<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HackUNT on Engineers United Docs</title>
    <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HackUNT on Engineers United Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/checklist/</guid>
      <description>HackUNT Checklist # This checklist is everything I can remember that needs to be done to make HackUNT possible.
This list is not in order it is just everything I can remember and will be added to as needed.
Hack UNT Operations # Typeform Set up for Registration Pick a theme for the event Make Sponsor Packet ( Use Canva ) Make Sponsor Onboarding Packet Pick a date for the event Set up the event on Org Sync ( you will need to keep up with this and answer their comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/day-of-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/day-of-action/</guid>
      <description>Day Of Actions # Check-in Station ( 2 - 3 People ) # This person will be in charge of getting Check-in operational on the day of the event.
Checking with Volunteers, Hackers, and Sponsors when arriving.
Be sure to be kind and understanding if there is an issue feel free to let ( Andy / Nick ) know so we can mitigate any fallout.
Check-in List Hacker
Hacker Badge Writing names on badges Team Name If they do not have a team don&amp;rsquo;t worry just remind them about the team matching channel in Discord and our Team Matching Event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/event-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/event-wifi/</guid>
      <description>Event WiFi # Event WiFi is supplied by the UNT IT department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/stats/</guid>
      <description>Stats # Stats must be updated yearly
It&amp;rsquo;s best to update the yearly stats as soon as possible, and or after the hackathon.
Yearly Registration/Attendess Stats # Year Registration Attendess Ratio 2018 ? 248 N/A 2019 498 258 51.81% 2020 558 220 39.43% 2021 ? ? N/A 2022 ? ? N/A Yearly Marketing Totals Stats # Year Ongoing Resumes Projects Attendess Prizes awarded 2018 1 ? ? ? ? 2019 2 250+ 192+ 200+ $56,900+ 2020 3 ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/volunteer-guidlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/volunteer-guidlines/</guid>
      <description>Volunteer Guidelines # Pre-Event or Pre-Shift # Familiarize self with Event Action Plan Have knowledge of severe weather safety areas at Discovery Park 1st floor Identify: Fire Extinguisher locations Automated External Defibrillators ( used to treat sudden cardiac arrest) Manual Fire Alarm Pull Stations at exits First Aid Kits During Event # Report to your section and let the previous volunteers/organizers know you are there for the shift. Ensure all guests associated with Hackathon have correct credentials ( badge, shirt, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
