<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineers United Docs</title>
    <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Engineers United Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/email-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/email-templates/</guid>
      <description>Email Templates Following up We should follow up with sponsors after our event. It is important to know what we did right and did wrong. This will better help us to understand the wants and needs of our sponsors. These companies were willing to give us a chance and give us a considerable amount. It is important that we try to mitigate all damages that might have occurred during the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/initial-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/initial-outreach/</guid>
      <description>Initial Outreach </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Onboarding Packet Sponsorship Onboarding is the next step after sponsors agree to participate in the hackathon! It is very important that you follow up quickly and respectively during these times. Sponsors will have quite a few questions but most can be answered by giving them the Sponsor Onboarding Packet.
What is included in a good onboarding packet  Nice photo on the first page Welcome page with next steps Have information discussing how to build a custom challenge, picking a winner, and offering a prize Have three goals you want for the sponsor  i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Sponsorhip Retrospective Following up We should follow up with sponsors after our event. It is important to know what we did right and did wrong. This will better help us to understand the wants and needs of our sponsors. These companies were willing to give us a chance and give us a considerable amount. It is important that we try to mitigate all damages that might have occurred during the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/sponsorship-packet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engineers-united.github.io/docs/hackunt/sponsorship/sponsorship-packet/</guid>
      <description>Sponsorship Packet Send this document during the initial reaching out to both legacy and potential sponsors. If this packet is done correctly, your sponsorship sells itself.
What is included in a good sponsorship packet  Main section stating we are a non-profit and go over our mission statement What is a hackathon Where are we located Make sure to include as many statistics as reasonable Table of Sponsorship Benefits Why you should be a sponsor section Explain why their sponsorship is needed Send off message (optional) past sponsors section  Examples  2023 2022  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>